today.  You already know that we are returning to
what we started to discuss earlier
about computer systems.
We have previously talked about
computer systems,
motherboards, and processors.  Let's
continue a little bit, above all, above
all we have uh we have been talking about Let's
see, this.  Oh yeah, wait, it looks like
I'm open in another window.  Just a
moment, I'm going to make sure I only
open one window for each thing, because
otherwise I'll end up with a bunch of
duplicate windows.
Okay, so I already have a headit
here.  Okay, so we've stuck with the
safety guidelines, and we've
stuck with the point that,
like I was saying, whenever you're going to open a computer, first turn off
the power to that computer.  That is,
make sure that computer, this is what I'm
recording, yes, make sure that computer
has no internal current and therefore
can give us a shock.  Okay, so with that
said,
let's get back to what we were
talking about, the basic components of
a computer, where on the one hand
we have the processor.  So, what
will affect your computer's processor
?  It affects the speed at which
your programs run.  That is, up to
this point, this will probably end up
being similar to what you
saw in the intermediate level.  What is the
fit with the higher degree?  Well,
we make programs and the
speed of the processor will affect the
speed at which the
programs run.  What is RAM?
Random access memory affects the amount of
information our programs
need to store.
So when you build a
program, not only are the first ones
going to be more basic, obviously, but
we have to worry about how much RAM
the program we
are creating needs.  That is, every time we
write a block of code and
run it, that program is
running against
hardware resources that right now are
very simple programs, and in 2025, the
default computer has
more than enough capacity to run
simple processes, right?  So, years ago,
decades ago, you first had to
worry about what the computer could do,
and then, depending on what
the computer could do, you programmed one
thing or another.  Nowadays, luckily, things are a bit
the other way around, but in the end,
we have to worry about it.
Hard drive, well, when your program
stores data,
that data will be saved
on a hard drive.
What capacity?
Okay?  Ultimately, all these
hardware resources are necessary to be
taken into account by
the programs we are going to create.  That
is, look, if here in programming
in the CCO unit we have reading and
writing of information, in
programming we worry about how a
program writes data into
computer systems, on hard drives we
worry about whether there is a hard drive,
enough hard drive space to be
able to save that data.  Okay?  This is
a bit of the link I want you to see
that we are making at all times.
Okay, let's continue.  Let's see what else
we find.  What else do we find in
processors?  Well, on the
motherboard, there
are also some
expansion slots.  This is usually
here, okay?  So there are
sort of slots
that are more or less shaped like this
where for example they connect here,
right?  And they plug in
here and they plug in here,
which are the expansion cards.  Not
all slots have to be
occupied, obviously.  Okay, these
are them,
let's see, where are you?
Here.  These are the
expansion cards.
For example, nowadays it is very common to
connect a graphics card.
What does the graphics card do?   It
speeds up 3D rendering processes
, not only for games, but also
for software that we may create
ourselves.  Either because that software
accelerates 3D, or because we use
the processing power of a
graphics card to accelerate our
programs, for example, with processes
related to
artificial intelligence.  There are also, and it used to be
more common, expanded sound cards
for listening to music or recording
music with even higher quality than the
sound card that comes integrated into
the motherboard.  What else do we find?
What else do we have as components?
Okay, what else do you have to say?
Tell me expansion cards.  We return
to motherboards and on motherboards,
motherboards
allow you to
connect components and have an
input/output interface.  What
components can be
connected to a motherboard?  Okay,
connector board, right?  Okay,
connector card, for example,
for more USB ports or for
different types of ports.  Okay, here
we have processors,
RAM,
hard drives, sorry, no, hard drives
are an input and output.  And let's see.
RAM, expansion cards
in the input and output interface.
Well, yes, what happens is that
cooling systems,
of course, how do we classify them?
Because they are actually either fans or
cooling systems, for example,
using liquid nitrogen, but they are simply
connected to the power control.
If they're low-power, they're simply
connected to the motherboard, and if they're
high-power, they're connected directly
to the power supply, but
they're not part of the data circuit, you
know?  So I'm going to put it
here.   I
'm going to put it here.
cooling or refrigeration systems
and I will simply indicate that they are
energetically connected
to the plate or to the power supply.   It's
true that some fans
connect a little to the motherboard
simply to indicate at what
speed the fan goes and in some
systems you can control it through
software, but it doesn't connect to the
hard drive, it doesn't connect to the RAM, it doesn't
connect to the processor.  Okay, let's see what
I'm going to drink.
Okay, motherboard,
input and output interface.  We connect
the hard drives.
We connect the USB ports.   We
also have uh ports
uh the old
monitor and keyboard ports.  On some plates they are
no longer there.
They are blue-green in color.
If you have an old computer lying around, you'll
still see that they were there.  What
other ports of entry and exit do we have?
Very important,
sound card ports,
speakers
and microphone
and it is not a whim.  That is, in
a computer system the
sound input and output is currently only being
used for music,
video conferencing and little else.  But
next year in interface design and development
we will see that inputs and
outputs are opportunities for
communication with the user.  Okay?  What
other input, input-
output interfaces do we have?   We
also have a small interface which
is the power
and reset button.  Okay, it's just a switch
, but it allows us to
establish a small communication with
the computer: I want you to turn on
or I want you to turn off.  Know?
Databases, right?  The databases
will be contained within the
hard drives.  I mean, we're talking about
hardware inputs and outputs,
right?  Ah, data buses, of course.
Okay, data buses, of course.
Data lanes are the information highways
on the motherboard that connect the
components.
Of course, there has to be a
data bus between the processor and the RAM, there
has to be a data bus between the
processor and the expansion card, there
processor and the hard drive.  I mean, of
course yes.  Okay, that's it.
Very good.
Okay, so let's continue,
and we can expand on this
later, but ultimately,
I think we're giving a
pretty complete perspective of what a
computer system is, okay?  that a
computer system, what you
perceive as a tower,
is actually a set of components that
all fulfill, let's say, a mission.  But
a tower, of course, obviously because at the
end it also has
a screen attached, it is an
input/output device.
Okay.
Okay, one screen.
And here I'm going to do
something very geometric, okay?
A screen.
And finally, the classic
computer setup, obviously, a
keyboard and a mouse.  I'm going to make them very
schematic, obviously.
Okay, a keyboard and a mouse.  I'm going to
put it here.
This over here.  This is a table,
okay?  And a mouse.
No,
and a mouse.
And I'm going to make a little bible.  I'm going to
make a very schematic mouse and that's it
.
Okay.  Okay.
Hello, hello, Dario.  Very good.
Okay, so this is what we know as
a computer system where
what interests us most about the
computer system are the components that
we find inside a tower and then,
obviously, what we are drawing
here are peripherals that
are also important because they are what
allow us to enter information using the keyboard and mouse
and the screen,
which allows us to see the
information.  That is to say, in a
computer system we are also going to talk about the
existence of peripherals.
That?  Yes,
no, no, yes, no, no, no.  Let's see, let's
see.  In the second year of
multimedia programming, which includes
a
video game programming component, we do see an
introduction to Blender on how to create 3D,
but not in the first year.  Now,
first of all, I'm just using it
to make a sort of
3D diagram of what I'm explaining.
Yes, no, no, not in this course.  In second
yes.  Okay.  So, in peripherals
we say that we have input and
output and on the one hand we have a keyboard
that allows us to enter
data.  It is connected via the port,
usually USB.  There are wireless ones,
Bluetooth, maybe, okay?  But
let's say USB.  We also have the mouse, it
allows us to move the cursor
in window systems
and in principle, as I said, in
principle it connects via USB, okay?
We have the monitor
that allows us to see what is happening in the
computer system
and is generally connected through a
visual port, such as
HDMI or Display Port on newer computers
.
Okay?  What other input and
output peripherals do we have?  Tell me
what you tell me.
Very good.
The fact that?  What have you said about
external?
Ah,
wait, wait, wait.  Come on, let's see,
let's see.  Just a moment, just a moment.
On the one hand, the monitor can be
touch-sensitive.  Okay, so then you mentioned,
uh, microphone that inputs information.
And for example it is a data entry.
I mean, right now here
you guys have just connected the
microphone to enter data into this
app, okay?  Via
audio port or USB, speakers
via mini
audio jack or USB.  There are also
USB speakers.  Have you mentioned the topic of
external drives, generally via
USB?  There are other interfaces too.
We do have, it is true, external sound cards
and not so frequently,
but external video cards do exist.
Uh, the USB 3 sound cards usually
work well, and the cards with
direct link or, let's say, with interfaces
faster than USB 3.
There are more things, for example, uh, of course,
you mentioned scanner, right?  There are
printers to print, there are scanners
to enter information, there are
fingerprint scanners,
okay?  for example,
for presence detection at
work.  There are cameras, we haven't mentioned it
before, my goodness, there are webcams,
okay?  And different types of cameras that are
usually via USB generally.
Okay?  In short, all of these
are peripherals that I could add to this
diagram, but obviously I'm not going to
add them all because then this would
become a mess of things.
Okay, I'm going to do this.  I'm going to
just leave this, I'm going to make it a
little bit blacker.
to differentiate the floor from,
okay, the computer equipment.  And let's say
we have a solid IT team
at the table, but there's a problem.  I'm
going to save this, otherwise it will
crash and I'll lose it.  Equipment.  Look, you
know what?  I'm going to save it in the
DAM folder.
Ah.  Ah.  HTML.
Dam dam dam d dam dam dam d.
Damo,
computer systems,
exploitation
and structure and I'm going to save it here and
team.
Okay, I'll save it there.  Okay, but what's
more,
if we poke our noses
into the following
teaching units, it
tells me about the characteristics of the networks.
Back in the day, back in the day when
I was little and I had my first
computers, right?  In 1985, 86 I had my
first computer, but there was no
internet, or rather, there was internet,
but not in Spain.  Okay?  So
my computer equipment was something like
this you're seeing, bigger,
heavier, less pretty, but it was something like this.
The concept of connectivity did not exist
because it simply did not exist.
The second computer I had, in 91,
90, 91, it was still like that.  It was already
literally with this format, but in
Spain in 1990-91 the
concept of
connecting through the telephone network didn't exist, you
could call, you could dial a
few servers in Spain, it wasn't this
web thing, right?  But we call a
few servers to do very
specific things.  For example, many people
don't know that in the 90s you could
shop online at El Corte Inglés
using a modem.  Another thing is that
very few people actually did it,
but El Corte Inglés had
that service activated.  And
then the internet came along and with the internet it
became normal to connect a bunch
of computers at different points,
right?  So the idea is that if I
'm in a house,
if I'm in a house,
I can have
over here, wait, I'm going to make a bigger void
here.
Okay, that's
more, that's more,
wait for it.
If I take all this
and I don't take the floor and I don't take the light, I
want
collection.  No, where is it?  A to
instance.
Oysters.
No.
Hey,
collection instance.  I should make you
say it at your instance.  Wait a minute.
Ah, move to collection.  A new
collection.  This is what I wasn't
seeing.  Okay.
Okay.  Move to collection.  New
collection.  computer.
This is what we were seeing.  Okay.
Okay.  Good.  So, so
you can
have a second computer and you can
have a third computer,
right?  And you can, as I say, have
a third computer.
The point is that when this
happens, these computers may be
connected to each other.  So we're going to
talk about network types, where you
're here,
we're going to talk about network characteristics
.
Ah, there are types of networks here.  Okay,
let's come.  Let's talk about
network characteristics.
introduction.md.
This video conference
is possible because not only do we
have software installed
called Zoom, but our
computers are also
interconnected in a network.
So, whoever programmed Zoom,
whoever built the Zoom program,
had to take into account that that
program was going to use something
called computer networks, right?
What is a network?  A network
consists
of the
physical infrastructure, equipment,
and software logic used
to
interconnect
computers and
computer systems and communicate with each other.
Let's talk a little bit about the history
of social media because you might be saying, "Oh,
history, what's that all about?"  No, I think
in this case it's going to be fun, it's going to
be a very superficial story.
Where would you say computer networks come from
?  What would you say is the
origin of computer networks?
Spoiler alert, you won't guess, but
try.
Right,
right, right.  Very good.  Well, very
well.  Well, very well.  So,
from here, the day after
the nuclear bombs were dropped
in World War II,
the Cold War begins.
The Cold War is about
the next day, this
next day is a bit figurative, okay?
Maybe it was the following week or the
following month, but the following day,
the moment the United States
proves that this weapon exists, right?
That they created it and therefore it
can be created and therefore the rest of the
countries might not have had it at the
time, but they say, "Wow, that weapon
exists and that weapon destroys cities
with a single bomb, something that up until that
point was science fiction. And
also
a front that seemed very difficult to
win, which was the Pacific front in
World War II. There were two
fronts, the European front, the
Pacific front. Okay, so all
of a sudden they win the war, I mean, they're
bluffing, okay? They throw a bomb,
uh, they throw another one, I mean, they throw a bomb
and the Emperor of Japan says, "I'm not
giving up." Okay, they throw another one and they say to the
Emperor of Japan, "We have a
few more, so you go ahead, bluff,
okay?  Because they didn't have a few more
yet." So the Emperor of
Japan calls the bluff and says, "I give up
because if they have any more of these, they're
going to wipe out my country and there'll be
nothing left." Okay? Another thing is that it
was a bluff, but oh well. Right.
So, so the rest of the countries,
right? Japan, because Japan is
kind of disabled, but the rest of the
powers,
especially
the former USSR, current Russia,
uh, launch into an
arms race,
because of course, the USSR says, "Wow, I
mean,
yeah, yeah.  Well, yes, exactly.
Let's see, let's see, yes, I'll tell you, the
issue of Japan is complex,
okay?  And it's hard to understand what
society is like today, given what we know
today.  Uh, Japan had
several things going on.  On the one hand, they had
the Americans pressing from
below, right?  throughout the entire
Pacific islands.  Eh, and then on the other
hand, well of course, Japan had
China and the USSR against it, eh, pressing on
the eastern flank, sorry, which for
them is western.
So, uh, of course, the bombs didn't
help, but it probably wasn't just
the bombs, but probably the
emperor said, "Look, bombs here,
Russians there, look, it doesn't matter, you know?
I'm piling up a lot of things, so
then they surrendered and then
after a very strong period of crisis
, then uh with the
Japanese character of self-sacrifice, which here in
Spain we don't even smell, well, they managed to
come out very high and very far
ahead. Okay? That's why I say that it is
indeed a, let's say, a
very complex historical context and that it
gives rise to a much richer analysis,
right? Well, then the rest of the
powers launch into an
arms race knowing that
the concept
of uh mutual assured destruction is introduced. I
mean, there's no longer a winner or a
loser. It's known that if there's a
nuclear war, everyone is going to lose. In
the sense that if the two big
players, the United States and Russia, drop
their bombs, it's not that they  They kill
each other, they destroy the
entire world. Because the consequences of
nuclear winter, between the radiation, the
temperature, the ashes, and such, eh,
a massive attack would affect the entire
world. Maybe Australia would be saved, because it
's so far south, but basically,
okay, it would affect the entire world.
Well, with which the United States
sees a system through the DARPA department,
eh, through which what they sought
was to decentralize
the system of government and
decision-making. That is,
if your entire infrastructure and all your
decision-making is centralized in
a single geographic area
and you drop an atomic bomb on that
geographic area, you
leave the entire country isolated and
incapable of making decisions. But if you
decentralize those
decision-making centers and at the same time
communicate them,
if one node falls, the rest of the nodes have not
fallen, okay? So, eh,
the concept
of a computer network appears
to cover two needs:
one,
the decentralization
of strategic command,
and two,
to allow communication
between research centers,
that is, universities.
Given that research
was one of the decisive factors for the United
States to win
World War II, for them,
research is
always very applied to the
strategic military field and ultimately to
having
a dominant position in terms of
technology, strategy,
and the army.
Well, from here on, from here on,
other countries
begin
to develop
their own networks.
I mean, they see what the United States is doing
and say, "Wow, it would be cool if
we did it too." But
each country's network obviously speaks its own
computer language
because they've built them
independently.
What is the Internet?
It's the union
of different networks
into a single global network.
Much of the Internet
adopted
rules from the United States network,
okay? Because it really had good
ideas and also because the United States
had a dominant position
internationally at that time. The
Internet, therefore, is a series of
computer systems that are responsible for
communicating computers throughout the
world, so that right now I
'm talking to you and I have no
idea if you're in Valencia or
If you're in Japan, because you could
be on either side, and
this video conference would be done
exactly the same way at the
user level. Of course, at the
network infrastructure level,
being in Valencia isn't the same as being in Japan.
Let's talk about that.
Regarding network types
, let's talk about the existence of
a first network called a local network,
called a LAN or local area network
.
LANs consist of a series of networks.
They're computer equipment
interconnected
around a
very limited geographic area.
Generally, a home, a company, a
university, at most.
What do they consist of? Well, they consist
of,
for example,
these computers being connected
through a central node
called a router, and therefore
each of these computers. I'm going to put this
a little further.
Look, you know what? I'm going to
see, this is a computer.
Okay, I'm going to hide this.
Visibility.
Hide all inside. Okay, perfect. Very
good. So, I'm going to create
an instance.  of this object
and I'm going to put one here, another here, and another
here.
Okay? So, when there's an
RX90,
this like this and this like this.
When there's a router,
well, that means there's a device
in the center of the network. I'm going to paint it
red, blue, whatever, and I'm going to
put
a lot of emission
that has a data transmission. I
've put it like this, okay? With light to make
it more impressive. Obviously, it does
n't transmit light, but it transmits data.
So, thanks to that router, all the
computers in that house are connected to each
other, okay? And they can share
information
when. Yes, yes, exactly. They're like fiber
optics, okay? Although precisely if we
see light, it's because the light isn't
passing through. It was more like a fluorescent light.
The idea with fiber optics is that the
light doesn't come out, but rather travels. But
well, yes, but it has leaks.
Indeed, it is a very refractive medium
and the light bounces outwards. Okay?
So, from there, we have, uh, a
wide area network. We have a wide area network
,
which is  One is a wide area network.
Many times, networks of this type are
VPN-type networks,
that is, networks that are separate,
but act as if they were together.
And from here
we'll see how the network gets complicated,
because for example,
you have this network, but you connect it
outside to someone's house. I'm going to take
all this. I
'm going to take all this
except this and this. I
'm going to do,
right? Where was it?
Hey, damn, wait until I remember.
Move to collection, new collection. I'm going
to call this house.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait a moment. Okay, house.
Okay.
Hamachi is, let's see, Hachi and the
onion and all that are really
systems to trick the network into
thinking you're somewhere else,
like a kind of VPNs or
anonymizers, let's say.
It's a strange thing. Moment. Hydro
inside. Okay, so now
I have a house and now next
I have another house.
And now next I'm going to duplicate
here.
Okay,
I have another house.  And I have another house.
How are these connected to each other? Well,
because our service provider
has a central node
somewhere in your neighborhood, and that central node,
let's see, RX90,
like this, okay?
So we supply electricity,
and that central node,
uh, wait. So, it
connects
from that provider. I'm going to extend this
further.
To your house.
Generally, that node doesn't connect four
houses, but maybe it connects 400, but
if not, this network scheme would
become unbearable.
Okay. And it connects 400
and so on. Okay. And so on.
And as I said, where there are now
four homes,
yes, yes, yes. The color of the broadcast
can indeed be changed if I do this and, for
example, make it blue, okay? And now,
notice that it's like a
bluer broadcast. Yes, it can be changed.
Obviously, if this is a zone node,
well, as you can imagine, this map
can be multiplied and multiplied and
multiplied, okay? By doing what
Known as a star network. I
mean, let's see,
star network for star network or
snowflake. It's
used to represent
very complex elements
in large area networks
. Let's see it.
I'm going to look here for a
star network diagram. Uh,
snowflake. I'll click
here on images of
computer networks.
Okay, it's a bit like this, but
let's see the diagram of the internet.
I'm sure you've seen it in
real life.
This one,
okay? This is the diagram of the internet.
This is the internet. In fact, this is
literally the Wikipedia page
for the internet.
That's a map from 2005, okay? Imagine
what it would be like in 2025.
Let's see. One of 13, right? This is the
original map of the internet in 1977. I do
n't want to download this file, I want to
see it bigger.
And well, and this is a bit what I
was telling you, okay? Each of these nodes is
the central network, country, city, neighborhood, and
all of this.
The idea is that the internet, if you
notice,
has  the structure of a brain, that
is, it has the Yes, exactly. If this
was in 2005, imagine today.
Indeed.
But the message is that
right now when we're doing a
broadcast through Zoom, we're
moving through this network.
Until now, it hasn't mattered to you, but now,
at the moment in which we become
programmers, we have to be
aware that when we program
network software, that is, when
we program software that makes some
kind of use of
network resources, we are creating software
that moves, that moves data around
this snowflake scheme. Okay,
so with that said, I'm going to save this.
Obviously,
the question is, how can this be
possible? Okay, let's take out the edit
again. This was
this here.
Okay. Components. Hey, where's
TCPIP?
Ah, network systems connection. Okay,
okay. It's in topic five. I'm going to
start introducing it to you. How is this
possible?
This is possible
thanks to the TCP IP system that we'll see
later,  Okay? We'll see that in
topic 5co, but the TCP system assigns
an address,
sort of like a phone number,
to each device connected to the Internet
so that each device on the Internet
can call any other
device on the Internet. IPv4, because of
course, you'll say, "Okay, how
can this be IPv4?"
has x.  X. X. Xe each x
goes from 0 to 255,
which means that with IPV4
256 actually times 256 * 256 * 256
equals 4 billion,
right?  4 billion devices
connected to the Internet.
IPv4, which may seem incredible
because it's like, oh my goodness, 4 billion
connected devices.  Well, even so, it has been
falling short for years.
So, we've had IPV6 with us for
years
,
so, wait, I'll ask the
GPT chat.
If IPV4
goes with X.x.x.X.
What is IPV6 about?
Ok, in IPV6
eight groups of axadecimal numbers are used
from 00 to FF FF.  So
IPV6
is what we said eight, right?  and y
where each y
ranges from 0 to
f.
Let's see,
128 bits.  128
is equivalent
to this is the scientific one, okay?
two
raised to I don't have it.
Let's see.   Oh
, it's there.
Well, what is
2 to the power of 128?
Well, 2 to the power of 128,
okay?   It
is 3.4 * 10 to the 38th power. That is, in
IPV6 it
is 3.
Yes, yes, yes.  That's why, that's why.  Exact.  This is what
is 3, 4 and 38 digits.  That is,
these devices can be
connected to the Internet.  In principle we
can think that with IPV6 we will never
run out of IP range.  If it
happens later, well, we'll see, because
later I'll tell you that there's something
called the Internet of Things, where you
can connect practically every object
to the Internet, so there wouldn't
be one Internet connection for each
person, but for each object, and there are more
objects than people, okay?  But
basically, I can tell you that in the context
of programming or creating
computer programs,
the use of the
IP protocol, the TCP/IP protocol, is very important because it
allows you to use an IP address to know what your
address is and to know what address
other computers have to call to obtain the
services you provide.  And with the
TCP protocol, you can connect to
other computers knowing their address,
obviously, and you can send and
receive information to them, and you can,
ultimately, share.  Okay?  I will
tell you later in point five
that there is a protocol called TCP, which
is where I send information to you, and another
protocol called UDP, which is where I send
information to everyone.  Oh well.
And for example, to send you an
email, the good one is TCP, and
to send a video conference that
anyone can connect to,
the good one is UDP.  Okay, that's all for today.
We finish classes for today.
You'll see the recordings uploaded in a little while
, obviously, and we'll continue on
Thursday.  As you can see, today's classes
are a bit more theoretical,
but they're contextual, okay?  Because
Thursday's classes, many of
you were saying, "Okay, we're doing
programming, we're doing
databases, we're doing
markup languages, but what's this for
? I mean, what is this? I know I
type something here in Python, hit
execute and something comes out in the
console, but why do I do this?
Today's classes are more theoretical, then they'll
become more practical, you'll see that
throughout the course, because in the end we'll
spend the whole course programming.
But today's classes serve to give you
context, to tell you that it's not just about
typing code, but you have to understand
why you're typing code and you have to
understand where you're typing code
and you have to understand who executes your
code, okay? I'm
telling you that not all the classes,
now at the beginning yes, but not all the
classes are going to be like this theoretical in a
document way, but obviously later we'll
start creating programs that
do all this, but of course, since in
Python we don't have enough
knowledge to do practically
anything, that's why these first classes
today are being quite  Theoretical,
okay? So, how much is
IPV6 worth? What do you mean by
how much? How much? In terms of what, I
mean, in terms of these devices,
but that's why you ask how much, I
don't understand the quantification of that
how much.
I mean, the IPV6 that is worth
different connected devices. Ah, that
's it, that's what connected devices are worth. Okay,
so we're finishing the classes for today.
In a little while you'll have the
recordings and updated on the medium
screen. Next week I'll start
giving you activities. Not for now,
introduction for now, okay? First
week and nothing, and I'll see you on Thursday at
2 and we'll continue. Yes. Question,
question, question.
Yes, yes.
Sure, sure.
That's it, that's it, that's what I was going to
answer. Indeed, at the end of
each class what I actually do is
open Jithub and then I go to the
Damd repository
on Damdow, no, on Dam 25 26 and then I
upload everything we've done today
and there you'll also be able to see where they
are.  the folders. And then I'm now
going to jubarsa
barra
dan 2526 and there, for example, everything I
was writing a little while ago about
the intermodular project subject,
well, I go to first grade and within
first grade I see that I have an
intermodular project and I have 001,
information search, identifying companies and all
that, okay? So, remember that
the premise with me is that you
can see everything here what I've
written, of course, because I
come here and I come to exercises and I
go to representative companies and you
have literally what I wrote in
today's class, okay? In other words, everything
I write within Heitel
or whatever, you're going to
have it, okay? So, don't worry.
If you see that you won't make it on time, apart
from the fact that the session is recorded on video,
okay? But all the text, all the
code, all the folders that I create,
you're going to have it later. I know
that this first week is a bit  Weird,
okay? It's a little strange, but you'll see
how little by little. The good thing about this is
that this is the outline of the entire course,
okay? Then the entire course will be the
same, so once you
get the hang of it, you've got the hang of it
for the entire course. Okay?
Oh, okay,
sure,
sure, sure. Well, that's it, all
the notes from last year,
indeed. So yes,
and
that was my intention when I made it
public. I mean, I could have
made it just for last year's albums
, but I made it public
precisely for that. So, what I
want to tell you with that is that in the
same way that I intended for that to
be visible and discoverable and
thanks to that you found mihub, I
will insist on you, not now, but in
the future, to do the same, that
is, to have a
Jithub profile and to put information
so that people can find you, okay?
With which I'm glad, I'm glad  You
tell me that because that was exactly
my intention,
okay? And that, okay? Well, come on, guys.
See you on Thursday. Practice little by
little, okay?